this um here's the deal I'm not doing
anything
outside that I cannot live
stream and when it comes to like
willfully choosing to do an activity
Outdoors I'm going to do live stream I'm
all sweaty right now because my car was
flat at the storage unit and I had to
change the tire and everything and I was
able to take my live stream with me and
they were able to back me up in fact JY
Jones uh and several others have helped
as J if he's got experience they gave me
some tips about some things that I you
know I've been I've changed probably 20
spares in my life or more and um
including on big rigs like when I was
doing the drive around as a river guide
and and my community just came through
they they were there for me they were
they were cheering me on they were
keeping me positive they were you know
helping me remember where I left my
credit card even um they knew that they
saw me put it down somewhere I mean all
kinds of things but here's the main
point and I'm putting this on YouTube
and I'm posting it to Facebook and other
places like that because a lot of
mainstream people are not going to
understand what I'm about to say but
live streaming is safer for me than not
as a as a person who likes to do things
activities in Solo um I'm planning
within the next five years I'm going to
be doing a bunch of traveling hopefully
I'm going to get enough money to get a
starlink and and I'm going to be living
in places remotely um I'm going to be
going on you know single s track if you
haven't seen the vods yet of me doing
single track some of the best single
track I've ever been now I'm able to
live stream it now and if I go down when
I knocked my teeth out my live stream
was there for me they were actually
exchanging numbers trying to find the
person that was the closest to me live
streaming is safer for a solo outdoor
adventurer like myself and you know this
is going to be a weird video for YouTube
there's going to be a few people going
to see that go you lost your mind people
can like Snipes you and all kinds of
stuff they absolutely can but they also
can't not know where I am so if I was to
ever get robbed or or or you know God
help me you know if everything anything
ever happened I spend a lot of time
helping the homeless and people get
really worried about that because you
know people who have had to deal with
the homeless know that that can
sometimes not necessarily when you're
when you randomly meet a person sleeping
in a trailer out out behind a a mini M
whose nickname is whatever the butcher
you know or or you know when a crackhead
makes fun of you for cashing in the
lotto ticket that some Karen gave you to
give to him and then they tell their
friend on live stream that they're going
to go uh cash it immediately as soon as
this guy gets done cashing this thing
that that actually happened um go check
the clips you know that kind of thing
you know if you're going to be outside
and you're going to be active in any way
um honestly I know people don't
necessarily like a camera in their face
but I've chosen that I'm actually
limiting the activities I can do based
on what cannot can and cannot be live
streamed uh there's only one really
serious exception to that and that is
time with my wife I spend time with my
wife doing all kinds of things and
particularly art events these days um
you will not see me live streaming those
art events anymore because those are the
few rare moments I actually have with my
wife who's exceptionally busy these days
and um so I cherish those moments and I
you know even if I'm able to I've
actually helped artists sell art people
have actually bought art through the
live stream um despite all of that that
is one exception to the rule where I
personally am not going to do that this
video is going to be linked from my rob
you know our skill. robob list of videos
about me and myself in the personal life
but I'm particularly interested in this
particular topic right now I know I'm
drinking beer too I'm drinking my wife's
beer my wife I told I said I was going
to drink your beer so now I'm going to
go walk in the rain and do the live
stream and go replace my spouse's beer
because Thou shalt not drink your last
spouse's favorite beer it's like a
horrible thing to do and um but this
again this is just an explanation of why
I think and I just it's really poignant
it's really the at the Forefront of my
mind right now because I was literally
live streaming you know underneath the
car you know finding the best place to
put the Jack and it's the things that
I've known my whole life but I was
getting tips in from people who are
actually experts in this while I was
live streaming it and it was amazing and
I am really grateful for that and I just
wanted to make a video about it that
that's it the
end um